Guide to the Stanford University, Center for African Studies, Records SC0832
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH-2006-217
  - FLAS:
    - FLAS Application Evaluation 1993 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Summer 1993 Wilmetta Toliver (Box 14)
    - FLAS Summer 1993 Walter Hawthorne (Box 14)
    - FLAS 1993 GJ Ferguson (Box 14)
    - FLAS Correspondence 1993-1994 (Box 14)
    - Readers' Comments 1994-1995 Title XI/FLAS (Box 14)
    - Tuition Shortfall Commitments Title XI/FLAS (Box 14)
    - FLAS Admin. 1994 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Summer 1994 Information (Box 14)
    - Hawthorne, Walter W. FLAS Summer 1994 (Box 14)
    - McClendon, Thomas Summer FLAS 1994 (Box 14)
    - Saulsberry, Nicole Summer FLAS 1994 (Box 14)
    - Draft FLAS Application 1994 (Box 14)
    - FLAS 1994-1995 (Box 14)
    - Datoo, Ahmed R. 1994-1995 (Box 14)
    - McClendon, Thomas V. 1994-1995 (Box 14)
    - Nicolette, Jodean 1994-1995 (Box 14)
    - Osborn, Emily L. 1994-1995 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Summer Applicants 1995 (Box 14)
    - Egensteiner, Eva FLAS Summer 1995 (Box 14)
    - Lane, Timothy FLAS Summer 1995 (Box 14)
    - Osborn, Emily FLAS Summer 1995 (Box 14)
    - Tunstall, Elizabeth D. FLAS Summer 1995 (Box 14)
    - Seidenberg, Philip D. FLAS Summer 1995 (Box 14)
    - Franchette, Lisa 1995-1996 (Box 14)
    - Gaines, Katherine 1995-1996 (Box 14)
    - Gaudio, Rudolph P. 1995-1996 (Box 14)
    - Osborn, Emily 1995-1996 (Box 14)
    - Seidenberg, Philip D. 1995-1996 and 1996-1997 (Box 14)
    - Toliver, Wilmetta J. 1995-1996 (Box 14)
    - Lane, Timothy 1995-1996 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Administrative Memos 1995-1996 (Box 14)
    - FLAS 1996 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Admin. 1996 (Box 14)
    - Budget Information NRC/FLAS 1996 (Box 14)
    - Bame, Ken Allen Summer 1996 (Box 14)
    - Barrett-Gaines, Katherine Summer 1996 (Box 14)
    - Hollis, Brian Summer 1996 (Box 14)
    - Huston, Jonathan Summer 1996 (Box 14)
    - Lane, Timothy Edward Summer 1996 (Box 14)
    - Seidenberg, Phillip Summer 1996 (Box 14)
    - Osborn, Emily Summer 1996 (Box 14)
    - Reports from FLAS Recipients 1996 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Applicants/Admits 1996-1998 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Admin. 1996 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Admin. 1996-1997 (Box 14)
    - FLAS 1996-1997 (Box 14)
    - Barrett-Gaines, Kathryn 1996-1997 (Box 14)
    - Hollis, Brian E. 1996-1997 (Box 14)
    - Kortenhoven, Andrea 1996-1997 (Box 14)
    - Nicolette, Jordan 1996-1997 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Form Letters 1996 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Memos 1996 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Admin. Summer 1997 (Box 14)
    - Cohen, Peter Summer 1997 (Box 14)
    - Downs, Maxine Summer 1997 (Box 14)
    - Hollis, Brian Summer 1997 (Box 14)
    - Lee, Chris Summer 1997-1999 (Box 14)
    - Lyons, Andrew Summer 1997 (Box 14)
    - Porteus, Kim Summer 1997 (Box 14)
    - Barrett-Gaines, Kathryn Summer 1997 (Box 14)
    - Pegg, Jacquelin Summer 1997 (Box 14)
    - Theis, Cheryl Summer 1997 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Language Approvals 1997-1998 (Box 14)
    - Hawthorne, Walter 1997-1998 (Box 14)
    - Lane, Tim 1997-1998 (Box 14)
    - Toliver, Wilmetta 1997-1998 (Box 14)
    - Lane, Timothy Summer 1998 (Box 14)
    - Drill, Sabrina Summer 1998 (Box 14)
    - Schler, Lynn Summer 1998 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Academic Year 1998-1999 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Admin. 1998-1999 (Box 14)
    - Adams, Glenn 1998-1999 (Box 14)
    - Datoo, Ahmed 1998-2000 (Box 14)
    - Green, Amanda 1998-1999 (Box 14)
    - Kendall, Nancy 1998-1999 (Box 14)
    - Mann, Kristin 1998-1999 (Box 14)
    - Lane, Timothy 1998-1999 (Box 14)
    - Carrol, Bidemi 1999-2000 (Box 14)
    - Higgins, Mary Ellen Summer 1999 (Box 14)
    - Mortensen, Holly 1999-2000 (Box 14)
    - Rhee, Michelle 1999-2000 (Box 14)
    - Shankar, Shobana Summer 1999 (Box 14)
    - Scola, Nancy Summer 1999 (Box 14)
    - Lee, Christopher 1999-2000 (Box 14)
    - Kendall, Nancy Summer 2000 (Box 14)
    - O'Connor, Kathleen Summer 1999-2000 (Box 14)
    - FLAS Academic Year 2000-2001 (Box 14)
  - FLAS, Faculty and Other Publications, ASA, SASA:
    - FLAS Continued:
      - NRC/FLAS List 2000-2001 (Box 15)
      - Carrol, Bidemi 2000-2001 (Box 15)
      - Jean-Batiste, Rachel 2000-2001 (Box 15)
      - Kendall, Nancy 2000-2001 (Box 15)
      - Malcolm, Makeba Zoe 2000-2001 (Box 15)
      - Mortensen, Holly 2000-2001 (Box 15)
      - Martin Herz, Susanne 2000-2001 (Box 15)
      - Lewis, Janet 2000-2001 (Box 15)
      - Bender, Matthew 2000-2001 (Box 15)
      - FLAS Summer 2001 Miscellaneous (Box 15)
      - Summer FLAS Applications 2001 (Box 15)
      - O'Conner Kathleen Summer FLAS 2001 (Box 15)
      - Peterson, Ingrid Summer FLAS 2001 (Box 15)
      - Rochefort-Reynolds, Ariana Summer FLAS 2001 (Box 15)
      - FLAS Summer 2002 Miscellaneous (Box 15)
      - Argo, Tracy Summer FLAS 2002 (Box 15)
      - Burrill, Emily Summer FLAS 2002 (Box 15)
      - Cordero, Iliana Summer FLAS 2002 (Box 15)
      - Berkeley Applicants Summer FLAS 2002 (Box 15)
      - FLAS 2001-2002 Miscellaneous (Box 15)
      - Argo, Nichole FLAS 2001-2002 (Box 15)
      - Burrill, Emily 2001-2002 (Box 15)
      - Carrol, Bidemi FLAS 2001-2002 (Box 15)
      - Patel, David FLAS 2001-2002 (Box 15)
      - Rhee, Michelle 2001-2002 (Box 15)
      - Zimmerman, Sarah FLAS 2002 (Box 15)
      - FLAS 2002-2003 Miscellaneous (Box 15)
      - Amari, Jealool 2002-2003 (Box 15)
      - Burrill, Emily 2002-2003 (Box 15)
      - Hill, David 2002-2003 (Box 15)
      - Kendall, Nancy 2002-2003 (Box 15)
      - Rhee, Dr. Michelle 2002-2003 (Box 15)
      - FLAS 2002-2003 (Box 15)
      - FLAS Summer 2003 Miscellaneous (Box 15)
      - Hesham, Alim Summer FLAS 2003 (Box 15)
      - Kane, Sheba FLAS Summer 2003 (Box 15)
      - Patel, David Summer FLAS 2003 (Box 15)
      - Williams, Melba Summer FLAS 2003 (Box 15)
      - Miscellaneous Summer FLAS 2003 (Box 15)
      - FLAS Budget 2003-2004 (Box 15)
      - Wilson, Elizabeth Olufemi 2003-2004 (Box 15)
      - Cohen, Jared 2003 (Box 15)
      - Miscellaneous FLAS 2003-2004 (Box 15)
      - Derr, Jennifer FLAS 2003-2004 (Box 15)
      - Hill, David 2003-2004 (Box 15)
      - Kendall, Nancy 2003-2004 (Box 15)
      - Petrocelli, Rachel 2003-2004 (Box 15)
      - Rhee, Michelle 2003-2004 (Box 15)
    - Faculty and Other Publications:
      - Newsletter Spring 1996-1997 Webpage Materials (Box 15)
      - Clippings (Box 15)
      - Web Page (Box 15)
      - Flyer Originals (Box 15)
      - From Protest to Challenge South African Politics and History by Karis and Gerhart (Box 15)
      - US Contributions to Peace and Security in Africa by Dan Henk, US Army War College (Box 15)
      - Mestizo Spaces by Mudimbe (Box 15)
      - "Case Studies in Education and Culture" by George and Louis Spindler (Box 15)
      - Moshi Proposal Intermediate Kiswahili Manual (Box 15)
      - Jansen's Book 1990 (Box 15)
      - "Life in Africa" by Vivian Russell (Box 15)
      - "Africa Through Literature" by Margaret Mark da Silva (Box 15)
      - "A Student Guide to the Collection of Art at the M.H. de Young Memorial Museum (Box 15)
    - ASA:
      - 14-18 October 1980 Philadelphia (Box 15)
      - ASA Misc. (Box 15)
      - ASA Africanist Directory 1982 (Box 15)
      - Outreach Committee 1986-1987 (Box 15)
      - ASA News April/June 1987 (Box 15)
      - Brochure 1988 (Box 15)
      - Women's Caucus Mentor File 1993-1994 (Box 15)
      - African Language Teacher Association 1995 (Box 15)
      - Ramphele Visit: November 1996 (Box 15)
      - ASA 1996 (Box 15)
      - November 23-26 1996 (Box 15)
    - SASA:
      - SASA Constitution (Box 15)
      - SASA General 1980-1981, 1983, 1984-1985, 1986-1987, 1987-1988, 1988-1989 (Box 15)
      - SASA Annual Report 1989 (Box 15)
      - SASA General 1989-1990, 1991-1992, 1992-1993, 1993-1994, 1994-1995, 1995-1996 1996-1997, 2003 (Box 15)
  - Samoff's Institutes:
    - Summer Institute 1996 (Box 16)
    - African Studies Institute for Undergraduates 1996 (Box 16)
    - Undergrad Institute on South Africa 1996 (Box 16)
    - Announcements/Applications 1999 (Box 16)
    - Knight, Sheri UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Penny, Lauren UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Pless, Zachary UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Steverson, Jenny UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Von Blasingame, Sara UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Whitgob, Emily (Box 16)
    - Wolfe, Jared UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - UISA Summer 2001 (Box 16)
    - Arevalo, Adhali UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Beck, LaToya UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Eifert, Benn Patrick UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Forman, Mary Ellen UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Friedrich, Claudia UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Neeley, Brandy UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Newell, Donielle UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Jack, Darren UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Katz, Joshua UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Master Copy of Packet for Students upon arrival UISA 2001 (Box 16)
    - Undergrad Institute Study Grants 2001 (Box 16)
    - On Arrival 2001 (Box 16)
    - UISA 1EUC911 Statements, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
    - UISA 1EUC911 Statements, 2000-2001 Backup (Box 16)
    - UISA 1EUC911 Statements, 2000-2001 Budget (Box 16)
    - UISA 1EUC911 Statements, 1998-1999 Budget (Box 16)
    - UG Summer Grants 2001 Samoff (Box 16)
    - 1EUC911 (Box 16)
    - UISA Teaching Materials, Handouts, Etc. 2001 (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous:
    - Nigeria: Country File (Box 17)
    - Guide Primary Teachers Social Studies Nigeria (Box 17)
    - Correspondence/Requests 1980s (Box 17)
    - Lending Library Books/A.V.s (Box 17)
    - Pearl Alice Marsh Chronological File (Box 17)
    - Jim Gibbs Chronological File 1985-1986 (Box 17)
    - Will Leben Chronological File (Box 17)
    - Cathy Dolton Chronological File 1988-1989 (Box 17)
    - C. Dalton Chronological File 1986-1987 (Box 17)
    - Frederikse, Julie (Box 17)
    - African Overseas Studies 1987 (Box 17)
    - TransAfrica (Box 17)
    - Announcements (Box 17)
    - African Culture Week 1966 (Box 17)
    - Jahn, Dr. Janheinz Visit 1964 (Box 17)
    - Budget 1985-1986, 1986-1987 (Box 17)
    - William Jones' Research Projects 1965 (Box 17)
    - OAS African Culture Program 1967 (Box 17)
    - Computer Compatibility 1987 (Box 17)
    - Fundraising Projects 1987 (Box 17)
    - Budget Request 1987-1988 (Box 17)
    - KD Memos 1987 (Box 17)
    - SLG Memos 1987 (Box 17)
    - Pearl Marsh 1987 (Box 17)
    - General Correspondence 1986 (Box 17)
    - USIA Secondary Exchange Program 1987 (Box 17)
    - 1985-1987 Miscellaneous (Box 17)
    - Abernethy Retirement Reception May 22, 2002 (Box 17)
    - Daily Ads 1994-1996 (Box 17)
    - Daily Ads 1996-1999 (Box 17)
    - Website (Box 17)
    - Stanford Bulletin 1995-1996 (Box 17)
    - Courses and Degrees 1994-1995 (Box 17)
    - Bing Scholars 1993-1994, 1994-1995 (Box 18)
    - Africa Focus Project (Box 18)
    - Chester Crocker 1993 (Box 18)
    - Salion Mbaye Sept. 17, 18 1992 (Box 18)
    - Sipho Gcabashe 1992 (Box 18)
    - Dean's Innovation Fund New Course Proposal African Philosophy – Wynter 1985-1987 (Box 18)
    - OE Research Proposal Hausa Idioms 1975 (Box 18)
    - African Studies Programs at Other Universities (Box 18)
    - U. of Zimbabwe Proposal 1991 (Box 18)
    - Fulbright Scholar in Residence Proposal Submitted Nov. 1987 (Box 18)
    - Multimedia Contract Agreement 1979 (Box 18)
    - President's Commission on Foreign Language and Internationals Studies 1978-1978 (Box 18)
    - Workshops 1980 (Box 18)
    - California Council on Social Studies Conference 1980 (Box 18)
    - Improving American Competence in World Affairs: Northern California (Box 18)
    - Exhibitions 1980 (Box 18)
    - CCSS 1970s (Box 18)
    - National Conference on Social Studies 1980 (Box 18)
    - African and Middle East Collections 1974 (Box 18)
    - Draft Folktale Unit by P. Kuntz (Box 18)
    - European Perceptions of Africa – Africa Education Project (Box 18)
    - "Globalization US History" (Box 18)
    - Important West African Europeans Readings (Box 18)
    - 6 Days in Soweto Curriculum Unit Development (Box 18)
    - 1981-1982 Miscellaneous (Box 18)
    - 1986-1987 Miscellaneous (Box 18)
    - Tamalpais Social Studies, Redwood High School, Marin County, Oct 1983 (Box 18)
    - Marin County Workshop, Dominican College Oct 1982 (Box 18)
    - Wilbur Middle School International Day, Palo Alto Nov 1982 (Box 18)
    - PAUSD Africa Workshop Dec 1982 (Box 18)
    - Redwood City Workshop Jan 1983 (Box 18)
    - Institute Reunion Jan 1983 (Box 18)
    - CCSS Conference, San Jose March 1983 (Box 18)
    - Cupertino International Day April 1983 (Box 18)
    - San Ramon Workshop April 1983 (Box 18)
    - Santa Clara County Workshop, Stanford April 1983 (Box 18)
    - Northern Africa Workshop, Berkeley April 1983 (Box 18)
  - Richard Roberts' files:
    - Miscellaneous Abernethy (Box 19)
    - David Abernethy (Box 19)
    - Students at Risk, Department of Education (Box 19)
    - Draft Summary of Long Range Planning Committee for African Studies Jan 1988 (Box 19)
    - African Studies 1989-1990 (Box 19)
    - Contracts (Box 19)
    - Contracts Symposium 1994 (Box 19)
    - Law, Colonialism, Contracts (Box 19)
    - Property Symposium (Box 19)
    - Inheritance (Box 19)
    - Children (Box 19)
    - South African Committee (Box 19)
    - Richard Roberts (Box 19)
    - ASA 1996 (Box 19)
    - CAMP (Box 19)
    - Law and Colonialism RF6 (Box 19)
    - African Studies TA (Box 19)
    - South Africa Exchange (Box 19)
    - Law/Bodies Abstracts (Box 19)
    - Francophone Curriculum (Box 19)
    - Francophone (Box 19)
    - African Studies Committee (Box 19)
    - ASA: Title XI Director's Meeting (Box 19)
    - CAF 1992-1993 (Box 19)
    - CAS Languages (Box 19)
    - Montgomery Gift (Box 19)
    - African Studies Bing (Box 19)
  - Visiting Scholars, CAS
    - Visiting Scholars:
      - Visiting Scholar Lists Per Academic Year (Box 20)
      - Requests for Visiting Scholar Affiliations (Not Granted) (Box 20)
      - Exchange Visitor Sponsorship Request Bechtel Instructions (Box 20)
      - Visiting Scholar Cards (Box 20)
      - Information for Visiting Scholars (Box 20)
      - Visiting Scholar Applicants, 2003-2004 (Box 20)
      - Visiting Scholars/Fellows: Listings from various Stanford Centers/Depts. (Box 20)
      - Asiwaju, Anthony (Box 20)
      - Austin, Kathi 1998-1999 (Box 20)
      - Berger, Iris 1993-1994 (Box 20)
      - Bourgeois, Jean-Louis (Box 20)
      - Buchert, Lene 1995-1996 (Box 20)
      - Cooper, Fred 1995-1996 (Box 20)
      - Crais, Clifton 1994-1995 (Box 20)
      - David, Roman (Box 20)
      - Diala, Isidore 2000 (Box 20)
      - Gish, Steven D. 1994-1995 (Box 20)
      - Golan, Daphna 1997-1998 (Box 20)
      - Haarhoff, Dorian 1994 (Box 20)
      - Holmes, Amb. Genta Hawkins 1995-1996 (Box 20)
      - Jansen, Jonathan Fulbright 2000-2001 (Box 20)
      - Jansen, Jonathan Re: Appointment 1993 (Box 20)
      - Jansen, Jonathan 1993 (Box 20)
      - Kiangu, Sindani 2001 (Box 20)
      - Killon, Thomas C. 1995-1996 (Box 20)
      - Konate, Yacouba 1998-1999 (Box 20)
      - Lance, James M. 1994-1995 (Box 20)
      - Lawrence, Benjamin 2002 (Box 20)
      - Lee, Ho-Young (Box 20)
      - Lee, Margaret 1993-1994 (Box 20)
      - Li, Anshan 2002 (Box 20)
      - Lirenso, A. Recommendations (Box 20)
      - Luiz, John 1999-2000 (Box 20)
      - Maphai, Vincent (Box 20)
      - Mauerstein-Bail, Mina 2000-2001 (Box 20)
      - McClendon, Thom Summer 1995 (Box 20)
      - Moletsane, Mokgadi 2001-2002 (Box 20)
      - Moore, Don 1995-1996 (Box 20)
      - Mutia, Babila J. (Box 20)
      - Obiora, Leslye (Box 20)
      - Okrafo-Smart, William (Box 20)
      - Pretes, Michael 2004-2005 (Box 20)
      - Scully, Pamela 1994-1995 (Box 20)
      - Simkin, Charles 1994-1995 (Box 20)
      - Soladoye, EE 1990 (Box 20)
      - Solarz, Marcin 2004-2005 (Box 20)
      - Windrich, Elaine (Box 20)
    - CAS Continued:
      - CAS Brochure (Box 20)
      - CAS Gifts/Donors (Box 20)
      - CAS Faculty Searches (Box 20)
      - CAS Property/Equipment Administration (Box 20)
      - CAS Projects MA Program (Box 20)
      - CAS Projects Overseas Studies (Box 20)
      - CAS Seminar 1964-1965 (Box 20)
      - CAS 1965-1966 (Box 20)
      - CAS Minutes 1976-1977 (Box 20)
      - African Studies Committee 1986-1987 (Box 20)
      - CAS Administration Correspondence from Committee1986-1988 (Box 20)
      - Long Range Planning Committee Ad Hoc/CAS 1987-1988 (Box 20)
      - CAS Projects Proposals and Requests for Funds 1988 (Box 20)
      - CAS Administration Memberships 1989-1990 (Box 20)
      - CAS Administration Invite to serve committee members 1990, 1988-1989, 1992-1993 (Box 20)
      - CAS Administration New Center Brochure 1991-1992 (Box 20)
      - CAS Committee Agenda 1998 (Box 20)
      - CAS Faculty Search Request 2001-2002 (Box 20)
      - CAS Committee CVs (Box 20)
  - Continuations of Title VI, Outreach, Conferences:
    - Title VI:
      - Outreach Title VI African Centers (Box 21)
      - DOE Grant 1985-1986 (Box 21)
      - Joint Center Performance Report 1985-1986 (Box 21)
      - Review of Joint Center 1986 (Box 21)
      - Title XI-DOE Performance Report Joint Center1987-1988 (Box 21)
      - Joint Center Performance Report 1991-1992 (Box 21)
      - Joint Center Report/Refunding Application 1993 (Box 21)
      - Title XI Budget 1993-1994 (Box 21)
      - Title XI Directors' Meeting 1994 (Box 21)
      - Title XI Reporting 1998-1999 (Box 21)
      - External Review DOE May 1999 (Box 21)
      - 1999 Proposal DOE Technical Review (Box 21)
      - Title VI Directors 2000 (Box 21)
      - Title VI October Proposal Guidelines 2002 (Box 21)
      - Title VI 2003 Proposal Review Comments (Box 21)
    - Outreach:
      - Africa Education Project Workshop April 28, 1979 (Box 21)
      - Africa: Differing Perspectives Workshop January 19, 1980 (Box 21)
      - Evaluations Workshop 1978 (Box 21)
      - Evaluations Workshop 1980 (Box 21)
      - Evaluation Workshop 1981 (Box 21)
      - USIA Nigeria Proposal (Box 21)
      - Nigeria Proposal Draft 1991-1994 (Box 21)
      - Supporting Materials for Nigeria Proposal (Box 21)
      - Boren Bill January 1992 (Box 21)
    - Conferences:
      - Conference Programs (Box 21)
      - Joint Center Conference 1985 (Box 21)
      - South Africa Conference 4/25/1986 (Box 21)
      - Spring Conference 1991 (Box 21)
      - Conference Panels 1991 (Box 21)
      - Spring Conference 1992 (Box 21)
      - Spring Conference 1993 (Box 21)
      - Spring Conference 1994 Cultural events, activities (Box 21)
      - Joint Conference 1995 (Box 21)
      - Human Rights Conference 1998 (Box 21)
      - Joint Conference 2002 (Box 21)
      - Joint Conference 2003 (Box 21)
      - SU-UCB Conference 2003 (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous:
    - FLAS:
      - FLAS Academic Year 1995-1996: CAS (Box 22)
      - FLAS Academic Year 1995-1996 2 Quarter Award (Box 22)
      - FLAS Academic Year 1996-1997: CAS (Box 22)
      - FLAS Academic Year 1997-1998: CAS (Box 22)
      - FLAS Applicants: (Box 22)
      - Julia D. James 1996-1997 (Box 22)
      - Peter A. Laugharn 1996-1997 (Box 22)
      - Jean Braithwaite 1996-1997 second alternate (Box 22)
      - Rebecca Rhodes 1997-1998 reject (Box 22)
      - Alison Norris 1997-1998 reject (Box 22)
      - Ken Bame 1997-1998 reject (Box 22)
      - Ann Woodward 1997-1998 reject (Box 22)
      - Todd Caschetta Summer 1997 reject (Box 22)
    - Events:
      - Events Fliers Originals 1989-1992 (Box 22)
      - Africa Table 1988-1989 (Box 22)
      - Africa Table Speakers 1988-1990 (Box 22)
      - Events/Fliers 1988-1990 (Box 22)
      - Africa Related Events 1989-1990 (Box 22)
      - Events 1991-1992 (Box 22)
      - Speakers File 1989-1990 (Box 22)
    - Conferences:
      - 1967 Stanford-Yale Conference on Senegal (Box 22)
      - 1967 Islam and the West Conference April 21-22 (Box 22)
      - 1980 Joint Conference (Box 22)
      - 1989 Spring Conference Papers/Planning (Box 22)
    - News/Publicity:
      - Newsletter 1988-1989 Events (Stanford) (Box 22)
      - News/Publicity 1989 (Box 22)
      - Daily Articles 1989-1990 (Box 22)
      - Newsletters 1996-1998 (Box 22)
    - CAS:
      - CAS Visitors 1965-1966 (Box 22)
      - CAS 1972-1977 (Box 22)
      - CAS 1977-1978 (Box 22)
      - CAS 1978-1979 (Box 22)
      - CAS 1980 (Box 22)
      - CAS 1982-1983 (Box 22)
    - ASA:
      - Directors' Meeting AASP Meeting Spring 1990 (Box 22)
      - Seattle Nov 20-23, 1993 (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous:
      - Language Center (Box 22)
      - Faculty Seminars (Box 22)
      - Fulbright: Dr. Yacoube Konate Cote D'Ivoire 1998 (Box 22)
      - Hoover Africa Collection (Box 22)
      - Africanist Faculty Guides (Box 22)
      - Previous CAS Brochures (Box 22)
      - Undergrad Summer Institute 1996, 1999 (Box 22)
      - Language Brochure (Box 22)
      - Events 1970s, 1980s (Box 22)
  - Audiovisual materials
    - Videotapes
      - African Studies Conference Plenery Session, April 28, 2001; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 23)
      - Panel Discussion on Southern Africa, 5/18/94; 2 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 23)
      - George Wright, "Angola: The Destruction of a Nation", 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 23)
      - Life of the Mind with George Frederickson, "Black Liberation Movement: United States and South Africa,", 1996; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 23)
      - Diamond, Ethnic Conflict and Conflict Management, 2/13/01; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 23)
      - Abernethy, "Democratization and Civil Society", 1/30/01; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 23)
      - Africa Table: Dr. Bartrom Collins, 1/18/95; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 23)
      - Ambassador George Moose, 3/16/94; 2 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 23)
      - Herman Cohen, 5/20/92; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 23)
    - CAS Meetings:
      - 11/16/83, 5/6/02, 9/29/03, 6/7/04, 11/05/01, 5/3/04, 6/4/01, 2/2/?, 3/8/04, 11/4/?, 2/2/04, 3/5/02, 2/3/03, 3/3/03, 10/4/04, 12/8/03, 2/5/?, 3/8/04, 12/6/?, 10/7/02, 1983-2002 (Box 23)
    - Audiocassettes
      - BAGEP 1982 Africa Institute, Joel Samoff, "Why Africa? An Introduction" (Box 23)
      - BAGEP 1982 Africa Institute, Professor J. Greenberg, "Language and History in Africa" (Box 23)
      - Kaijage, Tanzania, 5/7/83 (Box 23)
      - The Stage and State of Liberalism Struggle in South Africa 2/27/80 (Box 23)
      - Professor Ayele (Ethiopia), 6/4/83 (Box 23)
      - Ray Hopkins, 5/25/83 (Box 23)
      - Ladipo Adamalekun, "Guinea Revisted," 5/13/83 (Box 23)
      - Dr. Mohamed Hassan, "The Sudan, U.S., and the Middle East" (Box 23)
      - Ronald Hilton, 5/11/83 (Box 23)
      - Luise White, "Prostitution in Nairobi," 2/17/83 (Box 23)
      - Arnold Khavkine, "UN System and Economic Development in Africa," 3/2/83 (Box 23)
      - Harry Magdoff, Bag Lunch, 2/22/83 (Box 23)
      - Kanusikiri, "Zimbabwe," 5/18/83 (Box 23)
      - John Peal, 11/22/83 (Box 23)
      - Omansale Suttenwhite, 6/1/83 (Box 23)
      - Joel Gregory, 1/12/83 (Box 23)
      - Sheila Marks, "Health in South Africa," 5/19/82 (Box 23)
      - SASA Symposium on Food, 1981 (Box 23)
      - Africa Week Symposium: Alternative Development Strategies, 4/17/80 (Box 23)
      - Banegu, "Zimbabwe," 12/1/82 (Box 23)
      - David Hirschman, "Malawi," 10/27/82 (Box 23)
      - Van Olselen, "South Africa," 10/6/82 (Box 23)
      - Olaniyan, "Nigeria," 11/3/82 (Box 23)
      - Tom Farer, "U.S. Interests in the Horn," 2/13/80 (Box 23)
      - Bill Sutherland, "Southern Africa," 10/20/81 (Box 23)
      - Abernethy, 12/81 (Box 23)
      - Congressman Wolpe, 1981 (Box 23)
      - Kwaku Onafo, 2/4/81 (Box 23)
      - Africa Table:
        - Robert Bates 4/10/91 (Box 24)
        - Fred Cooper 12/5/90 (Box 24)
        - Jendayi Frazer 2/27/91 (Box 24)
        - Donald R. Sherk 3/6/91 (Box 24)
        - Jean Davison 2/24/93 (Box 24)
        - Kevin Danaher 3/7/90 (Box 24)
        - Gibson Kaman Kuria 10/17/90 (Box 24)
        - David Katzenstein 4/14/93 (Box 24)
        - Abdullahi Bature 1/9/91 (Box 24)
      - Conferences: